ILR School Librarian's Office Files /4004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Moore - Cottrell, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Moore - Cottrell, Gen. Corresp., 1972 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- National Council of the Churches of Christ Information Service, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- The National Institute of Social and Behavior Science, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- National University Extension Association, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Nation's Business, 1958-1959 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- New York Public Library, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- New York Telephone Company, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- New York Times, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- New York University Film Library, 1947-1955 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Psychological Corporation, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Public Relations Journal, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Recordak Corporation, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Student Newspaper Agencies, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Society of Visual Education, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- UNESCO Publications, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- United Nations, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- U.S. Government Printing Office 1958- (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Xerox Corporation, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- British Information Service, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Bernan Associates, 1964-1969 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- CUL-State Regular, Special Supplies and Expense, 1965-1968 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Special Collection of Research Material in ILR Library, 1943-1947 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Regulations Applying to use of Library, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Financial Record, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Photostats - Receipts, 1948 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Reference Statistics, 1948 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Order Statistics, 1947 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Misc., 1950 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- Replies received - To Be Filed, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Periodicals No replied received after two Months, 1951 (Box 22, Folder 32)
- Mailing List Requests - Outstanding, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 33)
- "Missing Issues" claims -Outstanding (Moore-Cottrell Subscriptions), 1950 (Box 22, Folder 34)
- Periodicals "Missing Issues" claims - Outstanding, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 35)
- Periodicals "Change of Address" Notices Sent., 1953 (Box 22, Folder 36)
- "Discontinue" Notices sent. Periodicals, 1951 (Box 22, Folder 37)
- Interdepartmental Order, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Interdepartmental Order, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Interdepartmental Orders, 1977-1978 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Interdepartmental Orders, 1977-1978 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- College Entrance Examination Board, 1960-1961 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Industrial Hygiene Foundation of America, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- National Safety Council, 1951-1964 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Negotiated Employee Benefit Plans Service, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Society for Applied Anthropology, 1962-1964 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Society for the History of Technology, 1963-1970 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Society for the History of Technology, 1968-1970 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Society for Personnel Administration, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- West Publishing Company - (Modern Federal Practices Digest), 1970-1972 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Hospital Personnel Management Association, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- American Labor Education Service, 1959-1961 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- American Foundations Information Serv., 1959 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- American Association of Industrial Editors, 1970-1972 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Adult Education Association of USA, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- General Correspondence Henry Strauss and Co., Inc., 1962 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Roundtable Publications, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Russell's Guide, Inc., 1957 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Georgia-Hanks, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Moore-Cottrell, all school offices, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Moore-Cottrell, Albany Ext. Div., 1965 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Moore-Cottrell, All School Offices, 1966-1970 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Moore-Cottrell, Buffalo Ext. Div., 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Moore-Cottrell, Ithaca Ext. Div., 1965 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Moore-Cottrell, New York Ext. Div., 1965 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Moore-Cottrell Executive Development Seminar, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Misc. Personnel Memos/Corresp. J.G. Miller, 1967-1969 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Inactive Student Assistants, 1963-1972 (Box 24, Folder 27)
- Acquisitions List, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Acquisitions List Compiler's notes, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Publications: Library Acquisitions List, 1969-1970 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- C. Library NYSSILR, 1949-1950 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Reader Survey Library Acquisitions List, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- American Library Association, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butchers Workmen, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- American Council on Education, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO, 1950-1960 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- American Management Association, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- American Museum of Natural History, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- American Records Management Association, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- American Society for Personnel Administration, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- American Sociological Review, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Association Films, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Association of Catholic Trade Unionists, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Avery Adhesive Label Corp., 1954 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- American Aviation Publications Inc. Official Airline Guide, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- American Education, 1965-1966 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Bernan Associates Standing Order, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- British Information Services, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- British Information Services April 1960- (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Bureau of National Affairs, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Business Education Films, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- American Hospital Association, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- American Institute of Management, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Capital City News Bureau, Inc., 1958 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- University of California - Berkeley, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Champion Paper and Fibre Company, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Civil Service Assembly of the U.S. and Canada, 1951-1956 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Commerce Clearing House, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- Cornell Alumni News, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- Contemporary Films, Inc., 1966 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- Cornell University Library State Funds, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 30)
- Cornell University Library Messenger Service (truck 714), 1962 (Box 26, Folder 31)
- Cornell University Library - College Funds Fund 290, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 32)
- Cornell University Library - College Funds 290.1 - Human Relations Project, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 33)
- College- Aid Chilean Project, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 34)
- Cornell University Library 291.1 Dastres, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 35)
- Cornell University Library Fund 291.1 Pedro Gugliemetti, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 36)
- Cornell University Library Fund 291.1 Guillermo Hori, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 37)
- TCA Chilean Group, 291.1 - (ICA-Rios), 1961 (Box 26, Folder 38)
- Cornell University Library-College Funds Fund 292 - Student Council, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 39)
- Cornell University Library - Fund 294, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 40)
- Cornell University Library - College Funds Fund 296 - Ford retirement Research Project, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 41)
- Cornell University Library - College Funds Fund 296 - Ford Retirement Research Project, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 42)
- Cornell University Library - Fund 298 - Nile Project, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 43)
- Cornell University Library - College Funds Fund 301 - Latin American Project, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 44)
- College-Bureau of Employment Security, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 45)
- College-Executive Development Seminar, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 46)
- College-Ford Foundation-India Grant, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 47)
- College-ILR Public Secondary School Grant - 1963 (Box 26, Folder 48)
- College-Fund on Automation and Employment, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 49)
- Cornell University Library- N.Y.S. Department of Civil Service, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 50)
- College-Other Expense, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 51)
- Cornell University Library - College Funds Fund 293 - Librarian Project, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 52)
- Cornell University Library - College Funds Fund 295 - Extension Charge Courses, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 53)
- C. U. Stores, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 54)
- Correspondence, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 55)
- Dartnell Publications, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 56)
- District Observer, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 57)
- Doorway to the 20th Century, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 58)
- Dun's Review and Modern Industry, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 59)
- Economics Press, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 60)
- Editorial Research Reports, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 61)
- Edholm, J.V. (Bookstore), 1954 (Box 26, Folder 62)
- Encyclopedia Britannica Films Inc., 1951 (Box 26, Folder 63)
- The European Community for Coal and Steel, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 64)
- Film Research Associates, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 65)
- Government Printing Office Jun. -Dec. 1955 (Box 26, Folder 66)
- Gov't. Printing Office - Jan.-Dec., 1954 (Box 26, Folder 67)
- Graphic Microfilm Corporation, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 68)
- Hall and McChesney, Inc., 1960 (Box 26, Folder 69)
- Harvard Business Review, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 70)
- Harper and Brothers, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 71)
- Holt, Henry J. and Co., Inc., 1955 (Box 26, Folder 72)
- Ideal Pictures, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 73)
- University of Illinois, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 74)
- Indiana University, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 75)
- Industrial Arts and Vocational Education, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 76)
- Information Service (National Council of the Churches of Christ, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 77)
- Institute of International Education, Inc., 1955 (Box 26, Folder 78)
- Institute of Management Sciences, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 79)
- International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 80)
- Issues and Ideas, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 81)
- National Railway Publications Co. Official Guide, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 82)
- Quarterly Analysis of Failures (Dunn and Bradstreet), 1960 (Box 26, Folder 83)
- Religion and Labor Foundation, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 84)
- Report on Questionnaires American Council on Education, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 85)
- "Subsidiary Library Book", 1969-1970 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Cornell University Trustees, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- B. -NYSSILR Reports of the Dean (Box 28, Folder 2)
- B. - NYSSILR B-5 Faculty Memoranda, 1948-1949 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- B. - NYSSILR B-5 Faculty Memoranda C-E, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- B. - NYSSILR B-5 Faculty Memoranda F-K, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- B. - NYSSILR B-5 Faculty Memoranda L-M, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- B. - NYSSILR B-5 Faculty Memoranda, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- B. - NYSSILR B-6 Faculty Committees, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- B. - NYSSILR B-7 Faculty Meetings Minutes, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- B. - NYSSILR B-7.5 Faculty Regulations, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- B. - NYSSILR B-8 Publicity Public Relations Affairs (Box 28, Folder 11)
- B. - NYSSILR B-11 Industrial Labor Relations Review - General (Box 28, Folder 12)
- B. - NYSSILR B-11 Industrial and Labor Relations Review - October, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- B. - NYSSILR B-11 Industrial and Labor Relations Review - Index to Volume 2, 1948-1949 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- B. - NYSSILR B-11 Industrial and Labor Relations Review - July 1949 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- B. - NYSSILR B-11 Industrial and Labor Relations Review - April 1949 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- B. - NYSSILR B-11 Industrial and Labor Relations Review - October 1948 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- B. - NYSSILR B-11 Industrial and Labor Relations Review - Index to Volume 1, 1966-1967 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- B. - NYSSILR B-11 Industrial and Labor Relations Review - July 1948 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- B. - NYSSILR B-11 Industrial and Labor Relations Review - April 1948 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- B. - NYSSILR B-11 Industrial and Labor Relations Review - October 1947 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- B. - NYSSILR B-11 Industrial and Labor Relations Review - June 1947 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Library, NYSSILR C-19 Personnel Applications-Professional Positions, 1947 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Library, NYSSILR C-19 Personnel Applications - Professional Positions, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- Library, NYSSILR C-19 Personnel Applications - Professional Positions, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- Library, NYSSILR C-19 Personnel Applications - Professional Positions, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- Library, NYSSILR C-19 Personnel Applications - Professional Positions, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 27)
- Library, NYSSILR C-30 Public Information, 1947 (Box 28, Folder 28)
- Library, NYSSILR C-30 Public Information Requests - 1949 (Box 28, Folder 29)
- Library, NYSSILR C-30 Public Information Requests - 1949 (Box 28, Folder 30)
- Library, NYSSILR C-30 Public Information Requests - 1948 (Box 28, Folder 31)
- Library, NYSSILR C-30 Public Information Requests - 1947 (Box 28, Folder 32)
- Library, NYSSILR C-35 Publications Abstracts and Annotations - Corresp., 1949 (Box 28, Folder 33)
- Library, NYSSILR C-35 Publications Abstracts and Annotation Correspondence - 1949 (Box 28, Folder 34)
- Library, NYSSILR C-35 Publications Abstracts and Annotations - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 35)
- Library, NYSSILR C-35 Publications Abstracts and Annotations - Notifications, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 36)
- General Correspondence Kraus-Thomson Org. Ltd., 1974 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- General Correspondence New York State - General, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- General Correspondence State University of New York General, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- General Correspondence The New York State Library Depositary Section, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- General Correspondence New York City - College, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- General Correspondence "O" Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- General Correspondence Ohio State University (The), 1972 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- General Correspondence Olivetti - (Travis-Westbrook, Inc.), 1972 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- General Correspondence "P" Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- General Correspondence Pennsylvania, Commonwealth of, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- General Correspondence Public Personnel Association, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- General Correspondence "Q" Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- General Correspondence "R" Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- General Correspondence "S" Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- General Correspondence "T" Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- General Correspondence U.S. Government, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- General Correspondence "U" Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- General Correspondence "V" Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- General Correspondence "W" Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- General Correspondence "XYZ" Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence '74-'75, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Library, NYSSILR - Special Projects Philip Murray Memorial, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Library, NYSSILR - Special Projects Sources of Information (revision), 1950 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Library, NYSSILR - Special Projects Indian Trainee Program, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 24)
- Library, NYSSILR - Special Projects German Trainee Program, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 25)
- Library, NYSSILR - Special Projects Latin American Project, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 26)
- C-65 Special Projects, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 27)
- C-66 Korean Library Trainee Program Mrs. Kim, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 28)
- C-65 Special Projects, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 29)
- C-65 Special Projects AID Chilean Project-Correspondence, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 30)
- C-65 Special Projects ICA Chilean Project - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 31)
- C-65 Special Projects ICA Chilean Project-Univ. of Chile - Library Material, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 32)
- C-65 Special Projects ICA Chilean Project Library Reports, 1952 (Box 29, Folder 33)
- NYSSILR - Library Statements of Accounts, 1972-1975 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Spreadsheets NYSSILR, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- State University of New York Memorandums, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- State University of New York Librarian's Conference, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- State University President's Advisory Committee on Libraries, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- State University A-3 State University Units, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- State University A-5 State University Libraries Personnel Policies, Classification, etc., 1960 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- State University A-4 State University Faculty and Staff-Biographies (Box 31, Folder 6)
- State University Chancellor's Committee on Library Development, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- A-9 SUNY Lib. Assoc. Council Minutes, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- State University of New York A-10 Librarian's Conference, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- State University of New York SUNY Head Librarians' Conference Syracuse, N.Y., April 21-23, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- State University of New York A-10 SUNY Head Librarians' Conference Syracuse, N.Y. April 5-17, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- State University State University Librarians' Conf. Albany, N.Y. April 24-26, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Cornell University AI-1 Administrative Staff Meeting, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Cornell University Buildings and Properties, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Cornell University Centennial Planning, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Cornell University A1-15 Graduate School, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- South Central Research Library Council, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Libraries and Librarians Univ. Libraries Newsletters, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Library, NYSSILR Special Reports- Monthly Statistic (Jan. 1971) (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Moore Cottrell Standing Order, Library (and other), 1964-1965 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Travis, Inc. Olivett, Ithaca Typewriter, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 21)
- Personnel - Misc. forms, salary schedule. Personnel listings, increments, 1968-1975 (Box 31, Folder 22)
- Pos. Descr., 1958 (Box 31, Folder 23)
- Cornell University Library A2-5 Inter-Library Memoranda 1960- (Box 31, Folder 24)
- Bernan Associates, Preliminary Orders etc., 1964-1975 (Box 31, Folder 25)
- United Nations Requisitions - 1969-70, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 26)
- General Correspondence - Labor History, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- State University A-10 Librarians' Conference Committee on Personnel Policy Hagerty-Newcomb Reports, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Cornell University Librarians, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Cornell University Cornellian, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Intra - University Memos, 1968-1973 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Cornell University Library Associates, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Cornell University Oral History Project, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Cornell University A1-30 President D. Corson, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Cornell University A1-30 President, Dr. James A. Perkins, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Cornell University A1-45.1 Social Science Research Center, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Read In - Study Center, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Cornell University A1-56 Board of Trustees, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Cornell University Library Bibliographical Records (Cornell List of Serials Project), 1962 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Cornell University Library College Librarian's Meetings Minutes and Reports (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Library Reorganization, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Reports Services to Non-Cornell Users, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Cornell University Library Indirect Library Costs Report, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Cornell University Library Acquisitions Agreement with Cornell University Library, 1953 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Cornell University Library Acquisitions Cornell University Library, 1947-1949 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Cornell University Library Acquisitions Librarians' Group, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Cornell University Library, 1949 (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Cornell University Libraries A-11-17, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 22)
- Cornell University Libraries Cornell University Libraries Employees Association, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 23)
- Cornell University Libraries Cornell Program in Oral History, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 24)
- Cornell University Libraries Ex Libris, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 25)
- NYSSILR B-3 General - Legislation, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 26)
- Administrative Memoranda Faculty Members and Staff, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 27)
- Library - NYSSILR Administrative Conferences, 1956-1958 (Box 32, Folder 28)
- School Meetings - Advisory Council Meeting, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 29)
- NYSSILR B-7 School Conferences, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 30)
- NYSSILR Visiting Lecturers, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 31)
- B-20 Faculty Memoranda - General, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 32)
- B-20 Faculty Memoranda Aldrich, Howard, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 33)
- Faculty Memoranda Dietrich, D., 1971 (Box 32, Folder 34)
- Faculty Memoranda Ferguson, Robert, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 35)
- Faculty Memoranda Gordon, Gerald, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 36)
- Faculty Memoranda Hildebrand, George, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 37)
- Faculty Memoranda McKersie, Dean Robert Bruce, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 38)
- Faculty Memoranda Morris, James O., 1974 (Box 32, Folder 39)
- A.B. Smith ILR Faculty, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 40)
- Publications ILR Review - Editorial Board, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 41)
- Extension Division Procedures, 1952-1964 (Box 32, Folder 42)
- Extension Division General (1970-) (Box 32, Folder 43)
- Extension Division Institutes, conferences and other Special Programs, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 44)
- Extension Division Courses, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 45)
- Extension Division Memoranda, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 46)
- Librarians and Libraries The New York State Library, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 47)
- Libraries and Librarians Princeton University, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 48)
- Administrative Science Quarterly Graduate School of Business and Public Adm., 1962 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Argus - Greenwood, Inc., 1977 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Bureau of Business Practice, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Chamber of Commerce of the U.S.A., 1969 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Clearinghouse for Federal Scientific and Technical Information (U.S. Dept. of Commerce), 1968 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Cornell University Libraries Acquisitions - 1970-78, 1970-1978 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Cornell University Stores Billings, 1977-1979 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Council of Profit Sharing Industries, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Current Contents (Institutes for Scientific Information), 1965 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Economics Statistics Bureau, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- The Federal Employee, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Group Health and Welfare News, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Industrial Relations Digest, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Industrial Relations News, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Institute for Social Research Univ. of Michigan, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Inter-American Bibliographical and Lib. Ass. Doors to Latin America, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- International Publication Inc., 1959-1975 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- Journal of Insurance, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 19)
- The Legal Intelligencer, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 20)
- H.A. Manning Co. of N.Y., Inc. City Director of Ithaca, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 21)
- A. N. Marquis Co. Who's Who in America, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 22)
- National Council on the Aging - Current Literature on Aging, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- National Observer, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- New York Times (Microfilm), 1963 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- New York Telephone Company April 1960- (Box 33, Folder 26)
- Pennsylvania Business Survey, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 27)
- Public Relations News, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 28)
- State Historical Society of Wisconsin, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 29)
- Training in Business and Industry, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 30)
- Union Democracy in Actions, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 31)
- Workers World, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 32)
- Old Requisitions - A Misc. A, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Freelance Abstractors for USDL Information Service Grant (Box 34, Folder 2)
- The Academy of Political Science, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- American Arbitration Association Requisitions, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 4)